Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Doctor Durand. It's not safe outside.
we don't know if it's over..
She's out there somewhere. I'm going to find her.
Dr Durand. I know where she was
when the attack happened. I'll walk.
I have to find her.
- Listen.
If your sister is dead. I'm sorry.
Then we can no longer help her.
But suppose she's alive.
where could she be?
She was on her way here.
- You have to wait here for her.
Come.
Hey...
I am talking to you.
Fred. give a bottle.
The number of survivors is unknown.
Above ground there is no electricity.
All the equipment that we were
able to secure works perfectly.
We prepare the generator.
And? Do you hear something on the radio?
- No nothing.
At no frequency.
Even the emergency transmitter does not work.
Keep searching
Where are you going?
Check the installations.
The satellites.
It was allowed by the colonel.
Okay. go.
Is everything alright?
I am thinking of my family.
Colonel. Listen...
Which channel is this?
It's not one of us.
We do not use this frequency.
Where is it from?
Somewhere North East of us.
I don't know exactly.
I've never heard anything like this.
Is it extraterrestrial?
I do not know.
Maybe they are already here.
Where's Dr. Durand?
Hello. What's your name?
You do not have to be scared.
I'm Catherine. And you?
Charlotte Fournier.
Where are your parents?
Dad said we had to flee.
I hid in a cave.
I can't find them anywhere.
Where do you live?
- In Grenoble.
I'm also going to Grenoble.
Are you coming?
Then we will look for your parents together.
Who is Sophia?
I just heard you all the time
call her name.
That's my sister.
- Have you lost her too?
Yes.
Maybe she is
with my mom. dad and brother.
They'll take care of her.
I've seen some dead people.
Don't think about that.
Just think of something else.
Be quiet.
What does that mean?
Who is that?
She has lost her parents.
Let her go.
Don't be afraid. they won't hurt you.
These are friends of mine.
Why did you leave?
- I went looking for my sister.
Her car is there. but she is not there.
Maybe she went back to Grenoble.
I can't let you go.
the may be another attack.
You don't have to come.
Did you want to shoot us?
We go along. but alone
to see what is going on.
You follow my orders. If I want to
that you continue or stop. you do that.
Is that clear?
Let's go.
Be careful.
We have movement
- Where?
Near the supermarket.
Maybe she's there too.
Please.
Okay. let's go.
Where is everyone?
- spread out.
What's going on?
lights.
Fuck!
Fuck. it's a trap!
On the roof. They're on the roof.
Stop shooting.
Only shoot when you see something.
What's on the roof?
No idea.
What is that?
Shh... Be quiet.
Cover me!
Apply pressure to the wound.
Stay with him.
Where's the doctor and the girl?
Did you see what it was?
- No.
Is everything all right?
Are you hurt? Where's the girl?
Halt.
What the hell was that?
No idea. It's gone.
Don't look.
Sorry. We have to leave.
It's too dangerous here.
We can't leave her.
I have men down.
I have no choice. Wait!
Said?
Sorry. we should never have gone
back to the valley.
I gave the order.
I should have protected her.
- You couldn't have done anything.
Have you seen...
what it was?
No.
But it has been waiting for us.
I do not understand. Why?
Maybe they see us
as a threat.
Are they afraid of a little girl?
- Or they want something from us.
They can find resources
on other planets.
Water. minerals. everything they may need.
It is totally illogical.
There has to be some meaning to them.
I'm going to sleep.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm